[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term hurricane indicates a tropical storm which occurs in the northern hemisphere, whereas this term refers to the southern hemisphere.", "correct_answer": "Cyclone", "incorrect_answers": ["Disturbance", "Typhoon", "Depression"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many years does it take for the planet Uranus to orbit the Sun once?", "correct_answer": "84", "incorrect_answers": ["104", "64", "44"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many times can an electromagnetic wave travel around the world in a single second?", "correct_answer": "7", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "5", "1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This hairless cat has a dog-like face and folded ears.", "correct_answer": "Ukrainian Levkoy", "incorrect_answers": ["Sphynx", "Donskoy", "Peterbald"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why were Eric and Shelly killed in The Crow?", "correct_answer": "Because of Top Dollars tenant relocation program.", "incorrect_answers": ["Top Dollar had a grudge against Eric.", "The villain crew saw Shelly and followed her home to rape her and killed Eric to get him out of the way.", "The villain crew saw Erics performance one night and they hated guitarists."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1996 game introduced networked play and 3-D graphics. What game introduced or perfected this landmark first person shooter according to Entertainment Weekly?", "correct_answer": "Doom", "incorrect_answers": ["GoldenEye007", "Grand Theft Auto", "StarCraft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the fast-food joint where Sue Ellen worked in Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead?", "correct_answer": "Clown Dog", "incorrect_answers": ["McDonalds", "Clown Burgers", "Chick-Fil-A"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Italian horror film, directed by Lucio Fulci, is about a series of murders that take place in a New England home.", "correct_answer": "The House by the Cemetery", "incorrect_answers": ["Mulberry Street", "Mutation", "King of the Zombies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sylvester Stallone made an appearance in this 1971 comedy movie directed by Woody Allen.", "correct_answer": "Bananas", "incorrect_answers": ["Play It Again, Sam", "Annie Hall", "Whats Up, Tiger Lily?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If a doctor prescibes a medicine and the prescription reads, Instill 2 - 3 gtts in OD bid.  What does OD mean?", "correct_answer": "Right eye", "incorrect_answers": ["Left ear", "Right ear", "Left eye"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1981 movie was the winner of the Academy Award for Best Picture at the 54th Academy Awards in 1982.", "correct_answer": "Chariots of Fire", "incorrect_answers": ["Atlantic City", "Raiders of the Lost Ark", "On Golden Pond"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ayurveda, chiropractic, traditional Chinese medicine and homeopathy are all forms of alternative medicine that adopt which of the following principles?", "correct_answer": "Holism", "incorrect_answers": ["Survival of the fittest", "Reductionism", "Trial and error"]}]